Guide to the Cornell Information Technologies records,1940-2009.
Cornell Information Technologies Records
- VM/IX Final Report, 1984-09 (Box 12)
- VM/Unix Memos and Agreements, 1984 (Box 12)
- VM/Unix Project Non-disclosure Agreements, 1984 (Box 12)
- Adesse Corp - CMS Writeable OS Minisk, 1980 (Box 12)
  - Software Support Agreement
  - WOS Documentation, 1980
- IBM PCCA, 1988 (Box 12)
- Computer Accounts (Box 12)
  - CCS Invoice, 1987
  - Renewed Computer Accounts, 1985-1986
- Educom Members/Representatives, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
- Data Entry Staffing Options, 1983 (Box 12)
- TMC, 1986 (Box 12)
- Production Control Reports, 1984 (Box 12)
- CNSF - Manual on Vectorization, 1987 (Box 12)
- CCS/CNSF - Cost Sharing of Operations, 1988 (Box 12)
- CIT Organization/Staffing Issues, 1989 (Box 12)
- CIT Review of Info Security, Policy and Control (Confidential), 1989 (Box 12)
- CIT Management Meeting on Copyright Software, 1989 (Box 12)
- CCS Kudos and Complaints, 1984-1986 (Box 12)
- Computer Security Reports (annual and ACR Alerts, etc), 1987-1988 (Box 12)
- Security Review - R. S. Vaught Chair, Security Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 12)
- Security Issues and Incidents, 1985-1989 (Box 12)
- Security Committee Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 12)
- Operations Exceptions Reports (daily, mostly 1985-1986), 1985-1988 (Box 12)
- Security Alerts, Locks, Issues, and Incident Reports across all systems including Vaxen and CNSF, 1985-1988 (Box 12)
- Budget and Business Office Issues (Bob Blackmun), 1980-1982 (Box 12)
- Output Measurement Issues, 1986 (Box 12)
- Resale PC Inventory Flap (Leo Collins, Auditor), 1985 (Box 12)
- Cutting Edge Computers (resale of Cornell used micros), 1986 (Box 12)
- Windfall Research Computing Allocations, 1986-1987 (Box 12)
- NE Computing Center Directors Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 12)
- CCS Management and Budget Office Procedures (personnel also), 1988 (Box 12)
- RFP for Campus-wide Telecommunications System for CU Mass Storage, 1983 (Box 13)
- IBM General, 1994 (Box 13)
- MSS - IBM Grant/Contracts, 1993 (Box 13)
- NSL, 1993 (Box 13)
- NSSF, 1993 (Box 13)
- Epoch, 1993 (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous, 1991-1992 (Box 13)
- MSG Group, 1991 (Box 13)
- Unix Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 13)
- MSS Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 13)
- ECIT - Exploring Careers in Information Techologies, 1991 (Box 13)
  CES and Chester Lloyd (5 folders in total)
- SHARE 76, 1991 (Box 13)
- SHARE 75.5, 1990 (Box 13)
- SHARE 75 and 74, 1990 (Box 13)
- SHARE 73.5, 1989 (Box 13)
- SHARE 73, 1989 (Box 13)
- SHARE 72.5, 1989 (Box 13)
- SHARE 72, 1991 (Box 13)
- SHARE 76, 1989 (Box 13)
- SHARE 71.5/71/70, 1988 (Box 13)
- SHARE Annual Report (Cecilia Cowles, VP), 1987 (Box 13)
- 1983 SHARE Report, 1983 (Box 13)
- Automated Operations, 1991-1992 (Box 13)
- Computer Disaster Recovery - Contingency Planning Guide, 1988 (Box 13)
- Crisis Magazine, 1990-1991 (Box 13)
- Contingency Journal (magazine), 1990 (Box 13)
- Automated Operations, 1989 (Box 13)
- Disaster Recovery Notebook, 1988 (Box 13)
- AIX User Workshops Manual, 1991 (Box 13)
  3 folders hold all the materials
- University Computing Board (Box 14)
  - UCB Correspondence Prior to July 1978, 1978
  - UCB Research Sub-Committee, 1972
  - UCB Minutes April-June, 1971
  - UCB Minutes July - June, 1971-1972
    Lots here on ARPA Net being promoted by Educom
  - UCB Minutes July - June, 1972-1973
  - UCB Minutes July - June, 1973-1974
  - UCB Minutes July - June, 1975-1976
  - UCB Minutes July - June, 1974-1975
  - UCB Minutes July - June, 1976-1977
  - UCB Minutes July - June, 1977-1978
- University Computing Board (Box 14)
  - UCB Minutes Feb - June, 1978-1979
- Report on the Interactive Computing Program; OCS report to UCB, 1977-06 (Box 14)
- UCB Agendas, Minutes, Issues ( mostly 1979, waning days of SAL)), 1977-1979 (Box 14)
  OCS Director search summary, etc
- Report of the Task Force on Computer Policy, 1979 (Box 14)
  Commentary by Rudan, Conway
- Medical College Computing Issues and Analyses, 1979-06 (Box 14)
- Refinancing the 370/168: S A Lawrence to the UCB, 1979-01 (Box 14)
- Visiting Committee (recruiting a new director of OCS by Bob Cooke), 1979 (Box 14)
  An attempt to find a director before going for a Vice-provost
- Functional Area Report, 1994-1995 (Box 15)
- Design Document/CIT, 1995 (Box 15)
- IR Quarterly Review, 1995 (Box 15)
- Transform IR, 1994 (Box 15)
  (includes John Hupp organization proposal)
- JWR Presentation to IR, 1993 (Box 15)
- IVY+, 1994-1995 (Box 15)
- Grad School Design Project, 1995 (Box 15)
- Office of Sponsored Prog Projects, 1994-1995 (Box 15)
- CAUSE Publication - Professional Paper Series # 1-9 (Box 15)
- CU Audit Report: General EDP Controls, 1991 (Box 15)
- IR (Box 15)
- Electronic Worksheets: A Hands on Workshop (Douglas Gale), 1982 (Box 15)
  (includes software disk)
- Disk Manager for the PC; Hard Disk Security and Access Control (R. Oakes and R. Cooke), 1987 (Box 15)
- MacRegistrar: A Specialized Database for Course Information (R. Cooke and T. Sobel), 1987 (Box 15)
- Library Technology Committee, 1989 (Box 15)
- IR Policy, 1989 (Box 15)
- Very High Performance Networking Overview (D. Lambert, CIT), 1991 (Box 15)
- Applications Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 15)
- Cecilia Cowles DEC 20 Project Team File, 1980 (Box 15)
  Including folder of pictures at the formal opening
- Comstock Academic Computing Physical Plan, 1986-1987 (Box 15)
- CIT Organization, 1989 (Box 15)
- CIT Organization, 1992 (Box 15)
- CIT Organization, 1989 (Box 15)
- Perestroika CIT Style (M S Lynn, VP), 1989 (Box 15)
- Applications Committee Meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 15)
- Distributed Technologies Overview, 1994 (Box 15)
- College IT Inventory, 1994 (Box 15)
- Services Division Transition, 1992 (Box 15)
- CIT Services List, 1990 (Box 15)
- CR Retreat, 1990 (Box 15)
- CR Quarterly Review, 1990 (Box 15)
- Disaster Recovery, 1993 (Box 15)
- Docutech Files (Box 15)
  - Docutech, 1993
  - Docutech, 1992
  - Docutech, 1991
  - Docutech, 1990
- Docutech/Media Services, 1991-1992 (Box 15)
- Amercan Community Cablevision (2 folders), 1986-1987 (Box 15)
- Space - CU Campus (Box 16)
  - General, 1966-1981, 1980-1988
  - OCS Management (needs/requests), 1978
  - Uris Hall, 1973-1987
  - Warren Hall, 1981-1983
  - Terminal Facilities, 1987
  - Upson Hall (2 folders), 1966-1981
  - Baker Hall, 1975-1976
  - Caldwell Hall, 1985-1987
  - Carpenter Hall, 1981
  - Clark Hall (2 folders), 1967-1982
  - CCC Floor Plan only
  - Day Hall Basement, 1974-1988
  - Day Hall Second Floor, 1981-1987
  - Day Hall Third Floor, 1987-1988
  - Day Hall 4th Floor, 1981-1983
  - Hollister Hall, 1985
  - Martha Van, 1981
  - Riley Robb Hall, 1981-1982
  - Rockefeller Hall, 1978-1980
  - Langmuir (4 folders), 1966-1988
  - Langmuir Facilities: 3081 Sale, 1986-1987
- System Availability/Lost Time Reports, 1985 (Box 16)
- System Availability/Lost Time Reports, 1986 (Box 16)
- System Availability/Lost Time Reports and Summaries, 1987-1988 (Box 16)
- Word Processing Issues (Cecilia Cowles and others), 1982 (Box 16)
  Includes WORDS the first and maybe last issue on WP (1985)
- Office Automations Plans and Proposals, 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  Office Information Systems
- Dean of Students - Office Info Systems Study, 1984 (Box 16)
- Email Items - early days of 1981, userids in Tel Directory, 1981 (Box 16)
- University Computing Board (Box 17)
  - UCB Minutes Aug - June, 1979-1980
  - UCB Minutes Feb - Feb, 1979-1981
- UCB Backup Material and CAG, 1970-1979 (Box 17)
- UCB University Computing Board, 1986-1989 (Box 17)
- NE Computer Center Directors Conference, 1985 (Box 17)
- Software Contracts for Cornell signed by JW Rudan, 1988 (Box 17)
- Memorex, 1971-1981 (Box 17)
- Computer Assisted Survey Program UC Berkeley, 1985-1987 (Box 17)
- IBM and Apple Monthly Purchase Survey and Stats, 1985-1986 (Box 17)
- CCS Operational Audit, 1986-1987 (Box 17)
- Security Audit (Computer Security at Cornell), 1986 (Box 17)
- Cash Balances (Box 17)
- J.W Rudan Mainframe Mailnotes saved from the file - Vaxen, 1988-1989 (Box 17)
- J.W Rudan Mainframe Mailnotes saved from the file - Coupling, 1988-1989 (Box 17)
- J.W Rudan Mainframe Mailnotes saved from the file - Security, 1989-1992 (Box 17)
- J.W Rudan Mainframe Mailnotes saved from the file - Barbara, 1989-1991 (Box 17)
- J.W Rudan Mainframe Mailnotes saved from the file - Action, 1990 (Box 17)
- J.W Rudan Mainframe Mailnotes saved from the file - Install, 1989 (Box 17)
- J.W Rudan Mainframe Mailnotes saved from the file - TC Bldg, 1989 (Box 17)
- J.W Rudan Mainframe Mailnotes from the files - AIXRev and AIX91, 1990-1991 (Box 17)
- J.W Rudan Mainframe Mailnotes from the files - AIX, 1990-1991 (Box 17)
- J.W Rudan Mainframe Mailnotes from the files - JWR1, part 1, 1989 (Box 17)
- J.W Rudan Mainframe Mailnotes from the files - JWR1, part 2, 1989 (Box 17)
- J.W Rudan Mainframe Mailnotes from the files - JWR2, part 1, 1989 (Box 17)
- J.W Rudan Mainframe Mailnotes from the files - JWR2, part 2, 1989 (Box 17)
- Pew Report (partial funding for CCC), 1986-87 (Box 18)
- Comstock Design (HOLT), 1984-1986 (Box 18)
- Comstock Construction and Contracts, 1985-1986 (Box 18)
- Comstock Annex Electric, 1985-1987 (Box 18)
- Comstock Furniture Plan, 1986-1987 (Box 18)
- Comstock/Caldwell Needs Analyses, 1986 (Box 18)
- Comstock Space Allocation (2), 1984-1987 (Box 18)
- Comstock Costs, 1984-1986 (Box 18)
- Comstock Move, 1986-1987 (Box 18)
- Comstock Miscellaneous, 1984-1986 (Box 18)
- Comstock Renovation, 1985-1986 (Box 18)
- Comstock Notebook by J W Rudan during the project (Box 18)
- Langmuir Relocation Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 18)
- Langmuir Project: New Computer Equipment-Construction Estimate, 1984 (Box 18)
- Langmuir Lab map, 1983 (Box 18)
- Research Allocations, 1984-1985 (Box 18)
- Windfall Computing Research, 1983-1984 (Box 18)
- Administrative Allocations, 1983-1984 (Box 18)
- Administrative Allocations Overviews, 1983 (Box 18)
- Allocation Worksheets, 1982-1983 (Box 18)
- Academic Allocations, 1982-1983 (Box 18)
- Research Allocations, 1982-1983 (Box 18)
- Computing Appropriations, 1977-1979 (Box 18)
- Administrative Systems Plans by Rudan et al, 1979-1980 (Box 18)
  Includes U of Michigan Admin DP Study
- Proposal for the Modernization of the United Way of TC, 1985 (Box 18)
  Computer Facilities by Joel Zumoff
- Tape and Disk Drives, 1984 (Box 18)
- Hewlett Packard, 1984 (Box 18)
- WordPerfect Advanced Course and Intro Course (Cynthia Frazier and Cecilia Cowles, CCS), 1984 (Box 18)
- WordPerfect User's Group Newsletter, 1985 (Box 18)
  Evaluations and Product Offerings
- CCS Management Meeting Notes, 1988-1989 (Box 19)
- Ken King Staff Meeting Notes, 1982-1983 (Box 19)
- JWR and Ken King meeting notes (5 folders), 1981-1984 (Box 19)
- JWR and Ken King Meeting Notes (2 folders), 1985-1987 (Box 19)
- JWR and Dick Cogger Meeting Notes, 1988 (Box 19)
- JWR and Stuart Lynn Meeting Notes, 1989 (Box 19)
- JWR and Stuart Lynn Sr Management Meeting Notes, 1989 (Box 19)
- JWR Notebook, 1985-1991 (Box 19)
- IBM Unix Evaluation Joint Study, 1984 (Box 19)
- Cornell A Capacity Crunch, 1991 (Box 19)
- Security - CNSF Security Committee, 1989 (Box 19)
- Security Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 19)
- CNSF Security Committee, 1989 (Box 19)
- Security, 1989-1992 (Box 19)
- Strike Task Force, 1983-06 (Box 19)
- Data Entry Transfer to CCS, 1981 (Box 19)
- 3081 Performance, 1983 (Box 19)
- IBM Contract; Wilson and Grimison Joint Study, 1982 (Box 19)
- XA Conversion, 1988 (Box 19)
- XEROX Corporate Visit, 1986 (Box 19)
- Presentation by Peter Baker to Printing Systems Users Group, 1988 (Box 19)
- Justification for 1st XEROX 8700 Printer in Day Hall, 1984 (Box 19)
- XEROX - Justifications to acquire an 8700 printer (RPI stuff), 1987-1988 (Box 19)
- Upgrading the XEROX 8700 to 9700 printer justifications, 1987 (Box 19)
- XEROX Desktop Publishing, 1986 (Box 19)
- CIT Security Committee, 1989-1992 (Box 20)
- Administrative Computing Issues/Reports (RS Vaught), 1981-1988 (Box 20)
- JWR and Alan Personius Meeting Notes, 1986-1989 (Box 20)
- Computer Allocations and Resources (4 files), 1981-1986 (Box 20)
- Windfall Computing from 1981 to 1986, 1981-1986 (Box 20)
- Instructional Computing, 1971 (Box 20)
- Administrative Expenditures, 1971-1975 (Box 20)
  Various items plus MSA Report by area from 1971-1975
- Computer/Computing Allocations 1978 to 1980 (2 files), 1978-1980 (Box 20)
- Computer/Computing Allocations 1971 to 1976 (5 files), 1971-1976 (Box 20)
- CISER 4381 - arrangements to acquire, share costs, etc, 1986 (Box 20)
- CISER 4381 - arrangements to upgrade, etc and CIT Budget issues, 1989 (Box 20)
- Computer Use/Abuse Policies, 1987 (Box 20)
- Chron Files for John Rudan Monthly, 1982-01-1984-12 (Box 21)
- Chron Files for John Rudan Monthly, 1980-01-1981-09 (Box 22)
- JW Rudan Chron Files, 1981-10-1981-12 (Box 23)
- MSA Chron Files (Box 23)
  - Al Seliga, 1974-1976, 1977-1978
  - Bruce Lloyd, 1975-1976
  - Libby Gruppuso, 1975, 1977-1978
  - Tom Dimock, 1975-1978
  - Claude Garner, 1977
  - Jim Storelli, 1975, 1977
  - Joel Zumoff, 1975-1977
- Chron Files for John Rudan Monthly, 1985-01-1989-01 (Box 23)
- IBM Charging for SLSS - Systems Library Subscriptions, 1986 (Box 23)
- IBM Correspondence, etc (Mainframes, CIT/TC) 1985-87, 1985-1987 (Box 23)
  Includes shock testing for effects when drilling elevator shaft
- IBM Technical Documents - 3090, MVS/XA, 3044 Optic Link,etc, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
- IBM Replacing 3174 Controllers in CIT m/c room, 1986 (Box 23)
- IBM Correspondence, etc (Mainframes, CIT/TC) and Netview (1), 1988 (Box 23)
- IBM Correspondence, etc (Mainframes, CIT/TC) and ES 3090 (2), 1988 (Box 23)
- IBM Correspondence, etc (Large Systems, CIT/TC), 1987 (Box 23)
- IBM Workstation Resource Center Planning and Implementation Guide, 1984 (Box 23)
- IBM Cambridge Scientific Center Experimental Approach to the Remote Operation, Mgmt, Control of Distributed Processors with VM/370, 1982 (Box 23)
- IBM Input/Output Device Summary Manual, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
- CCS Budget, 1987 (Box 24)
- Budget (2 folders), 1988-1989 (Box 24)
- Adabas Performance, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
- 3081 Performance, 1984 (Box 24)
- Data Migration, 1984-1986 (Box 24)
- DASD Planning, 1984-1985 (Box 24)
- 3375 to 3380, 1984-1985 (Box 24)
- MVS Space Planning, 1984 (Box 24)
- DASD, 1983-1984 (Box 24)
- Compensation Study, Project Document, Plan, Steps, etc, 1983-1984 (Box 24)
- Compensation Study, Results, etc, 1983-1984 (Box 24)
- Reclassification Study, Non-exempt Staff, 1984-1985 (Box 24)
- Employee Issues, Events, Special Items, etc, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
- CIT Reorganization, 1989 (Box 24)
- CIT Position Classification, 1988 (Box 24)
- Plans and Project Lists, 1983-1985 (Box 24)
- Saltford Report/Computer Costs, 1987 (Box 24)
- SAS and Miscellaneous Software, 1980 (Box 24)
- Telecom/Tymnet Plan, 1980 (Box 24)
- Coopers and Lybrand Audit, 1984 (Box 24)
- Comp Center Priority Projects, 1987-1988 (Box 24)
- Adabas and Shadow II, 1980-1983 (Box 24)
- 4341B Sales, 1983 (Box 24)
- 4341B Offers, 1983 (Box 24)
- SCI/OCS license, 1976 (Box 24)
- Graduate School Admissions System, 1979 (Box 24)
- Sponsored Research IBM 5120 System, 1980 (Box 24)
- Compensatory Time Procedures, 1980-1982 (Box 24)
- TBAR, 1980 (Box 24)
- Capacity Planning, 1979 (Box 24)
- Computer Software Policy, 1981 (Box 24)
- Software Sales, 1981-1982 (Box 24)
- Capital Budget/Space Planning, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
- OCS Budget Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
- OCS Policies and Procedure Manual, 1974 (Box 24)
- IBM Loaner Program and Marketing Deals, 1986 (Box 24)
- IBM PS/2 Announcement, 1987 (Box 24)
- IBM HESC Program - Higher Education Software Consortium, 1988 (Box 24)
- IBM Confidentiality to Cornell - Chris McMahon, 1992 (Box 24)
- Sloan Management Review - Reprint Series, 1992 (Box 24)
  Systems Delivery: Evolving New Strategies, Critical IT Issues: The Next Ten Years
- Harvard Business Review, 1989-1990 (Box 24)
  Reengineering Work: Don't Automate, Obliterate by Michael Hammer, How Executives Can Shape their Company's Information Systems
- Computing Center Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 25)
- Budget Development, 1989-1990 (Box 25)
- CCS Budget (3 folders), 1988-1989 (Box 25)
- Budget and Networking Misc, 1979-1980 (Box 25)
- Network Communications Budget, 1986 (Box 25)
- Corning, 1985 (Box 25)
- DACU-AT/Wehrle Project, 1986-1987 (Box 25)
- Network Planning: Fiber Installation, Pronet, Node Rooms, etc, 1984-1986 (Box 25)
- Network Planning, 1987 (Box 25)
- Line Mode, 1988 (Box 25)
- Remote Network Rooms, 1985 (Box 25)
- David Lytel, 1988 (Box 25)
- NYNEX, 1988 (Box 25)
- Net Architecture, 1988 (Box 25)
- Net Council, 1988 (Box 25)
- Networking/ Pat Paul Meeting - Telecomm Issues, 1988 (Box 25)
- ULTRA, 1989 (Box 25)
- Benchmarks, 1986-1987 (Box 25)
- Network Plans, 1985-1987 (Box 25)
- Net Rates, 1987-1988 (Box 25)
- Notables, 1987-1988 (Box 25)
- Networking Consulting Group, 1987 (Box 25)
- Wiscnet, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
- NYSERNET: Geneva Extension, 1989 (Box 25)
- NYSERNET News (newsletter) and PSI, 1989 (Box 25)
- Network Council (3 folders), 1987-1989 (Box 25)
- Networking, 1988-1989 (Box 25)
- Wiscnet and IBM TCP/IP A Performance Perspective, 1988 (Box 25)
- System Programming Unit Plans/Schedules, 1987 (Box 25)
- Apple and Network Communications, 1987 (Box 25)
- Super Computer Network (newsletter for supercomputer users), 1989-03 (Box 26)
- NSF/IBM Supercomputing Proposal, 1989 (Box 26)
- Science and Supercomputing on the CNSF (pub), 1989 (Box 26)
- On Overview of the CNSF: A Guide for New Users (pub), 1989 (Box 26)
- Cornell Theory Center and SSI Corporation Proposal, 1988 (Box 26)
- Cornell Theory Center: 5 year Renewal Proposal to NSF, 1991-1995 (Box 26)
- Cornell Supercomputer Proposals, 1989 (Box 26)
- PSF (Production Supercomputer Facility) Availability, Operations, etc, 1985 (Box 26)
- Cornell-IBM: PSF Planning Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 26)
- CNSF - Cornell University Supercomputer Facility, 1986 (Box 26)
- § CNSF - the early days, startup stuff, 1984 (Box 26)
- The Univ/Industry Supercomputer Connection Conference, 1986-10 (Box 26)
- 56 Kbit, 1986 (Box 26)
- PSF Users Meetings, 1986 (Box 26)
- Cornell Theory Center Summary Report, 1987 (Box 26)
- CNSF, 1987 (Box 26)
- Cornell Theory Center, 1987 (Box 26)
- IBM Supercomputing Technology Center at Cornell University, 1989-12 (Box 26)
  Bios of the IBM Support team staff members at Cornell
- Haworth Product Presentation, 1986 (Box 26)
- CISER rates, 1986-1987 (Box 26)
- Rates, 1986 (Box 26)
- GCA - General Computing Accounts (Box 26)
  - GCA Migration, 1992-1993
  - GCA Migration Phase II/CCDs, 1992
  - GCA Migration People, 1990
  - GCA Migration Presentations w Overheads, 1992-1994
  - GCA Migration Budget, 1993-1994
  - GCA Migration Usage, 1993
  - GCA Conversion, 1993
  - GCA Migration, 1992-1993
  - GCA Migration and Bear Access and Services, 1992
  - GCA Migration Team Report (early ones), 1994
  - Bear Access Documentation
- CIT Retreat, 1991 (Box 27)
- Retreat Agendas/Memos, 1991 (Box 27)
- Sr Mgmt Meetings, 1989-1991 (Box 27)
- Sr Mgmt Meetings, 1990, 1991, 1993, 1995 (Box 27)
- Sr Mgmt Action Logs, 1989 (Box 27)
- Management Issues, 1988 (Box 27)
- Sr Mgmt/AD Presentations, 1989 (Box 27)
- Sr Mgmt Presentation (D W Pulleyn), 1990 (Box 27)
- Sr Mgmt/AD Presentations, 1990 (Box 27)
- Sr Mgmt Presentation - Network Resources, 1990 (Box 27)
- Classification Review Study, 1992 (Box 27)
- IR Budget, 1989 (Box 27)
- IR Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 27)
- IR Budget, 1992 (Box 27)
- John Hupp on Information Project Leadership, 1992 (Box 27)
  Developing Quality Information Services
- CAUCUS 95 at the College of William and Mary, 1995-05 (Box 27)
  Kevin Hufford on Data Warehouses, Ron Babuka on Printing Claudia Wodzinksi on Legacy to Client/Server Chris Brown on Empowered Teams
- CIT's Evolving Structure - Meeting its Long Term Vision, 1992-04 (Box 27)
  Report on organizing CIT by 5 grad students to M. Stuart Lynn
- IR Methodology Vol 2, Guide to Deliverables and Methods, 1993-03 (Box 27)
- Reorganizing CR - Team based organization, 1994 (Box 27)
- CCS Staff Activity Reports (variety), 1985-1986 (Box 27)
- Ken King Computing Plan, 1980 (Box 27)
- KK/JWR Correspondence, 1980 (Box 27)
  Including a prospectus for Academic Computing by Van Houweling and Grimison
- Drobin Report to KK, 1980 (Box 27)
- Management Issues - stats (IT), admin comp, other good stuff., 1981-1982 (Box 27)
  - Ken King CCS Organization Chart and Proposals, 1981-06
- Ken King Proposed Organization Chart, 1981-06 (Box 27)
- JWR Monthly Planners and Calendars, 1971-1981 (Box 28)
- Bob Cowles' notebooks, 1972-1976,1982-1992 (Box 28)
- N OCS Memorandums, 1967 -1969 (Box 28)
- N OCS Memorandums, 1968 -1970 (Box 28)
- OCS Memorandums, 1970-1971 (Box 28)
- OCS Staff News, 1970 (Box 28)
- OCS Management, 1974-1976 (Box 28)
- Miscellaneous OCS Forms, 1968 (Box 28)
- Planning at Cornell, 1977-1978 (Box 28)
- IPA Cornell Facts and Studies, 1974-1979 (Box 28)
- Mgmt Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box 28)
- Mgmt Meeting Minutes, 1974 (Box 28)
- SAL/JWR, 1977-1982 (Box 28)
- Correspondence to R A Plane, Provost, 1969-1970 (Box 28)
- JWR Speeches, Talks, etc, 1979 (Box 28)
- JWR Former Staff, Letters, etc, 1972-1982 (Box 28)
- CAUSE Conferences and Materials, 1973-1977 (Box 28)
- Data Network for Cornell (CCS), 1978 (Box 28)
- Computer Security at Cornell, 1978 (Box 28)
- Decisions of the Tribal Council (systems/ops meetings), 1972 (Box 28)
- MSA Materials (Box 29)
  - Design Specification for the ACT/SISELECT subsystem, 1974
  - Design Specification for the Missing Records Program, 1974
  - Design Specification for the EAS Tuition Program, 1974
  - Design Specification for the Statistics File Extract Program, 1974
  - Design Specification for the EAS Biographic File Extract Program, 1974
  - Design Specification for the Motor Vehicle Data Base, 1974
  - Guide to Operating the Hazeltine 2000 Terminal, 1974
  - Interim Summer Session Registration System, 1972
  - Proposed CU Student Records, Registration and Schedule Systems, 1975
- SCT: Systems and Computer Technology Corporation (Box 29)
  - Correspondence - Registrar's Office, 1974
  - Correspondence - MSA's office, 1973-1974
  - J. A. Campbell Chronological File, 1973-1974
  - H G Vaughan Chron File, 1973-1974
  - Correspondence, 1972-1973
  - Correspondence, 1973-1974
  - Correspondence, 1974-1975
  - SCT Agreement, 1973
  - Annual Reports and Goals, 1978
  - Joint Study; Future Plans for Student Interactive computing, 1979
    IBM Cambridge Lab for CMS - Grimison proposal
  - Administrative System Descriptions, 1980
  - Payroll/Personnel Project, 1971
  - IMS Data Management System, 1970
  - UCB, 1976
  - Admin System Activity, 1971
  - Project Leader Presentations-Admin Systems, 1968
  - Alumni News proposed system, 1977-1978
  - The Future of Administrative Computing at Cornell, 1973
    Tentative Long-range plans Mgmt systems by H. G Vaughan
  - HASP Job Cards (Ron Roberts), 1972-10
  - HASP vs CLASP Report from OCS Management (2 copies), 1970-11
  - HASP - A new software system at Cornell - OCS Announcement, 1971
  - HASP Operation Reports, 1970
- Funding Opportunities: Income, 1977 (Box 30)
- NBER Contract Negotiations, 1977 (Box 30)
- NBER Contacts, 1975-1976 (Box 30)
- PBM/STIRS - reports, costs, 1977 (Box 30)
- Capacity Planning (2 files), 1977-1978 (Box 30)
- SECOS Termination, 1978 (Box 30)
  Shared Educational Computing System
- SECOS Contract Draft, 1978-1979 (Box 30)
- SECOS-CUMC Proposal, 1977 (Box 30)
- CUMC Agreement, 1981 (Box 30)
- CUMC - Cornell University Medical College (Box 30)
  - Correspondence, Documents (Except 1976), 1975-1980
  - Conversion Proposal, 1978
- 360/65 Sale and TLW Lawsuit, 1975 (Box 30)
- 360/67 IBM Proposal to CU, 1965 (Box 30)
- 3605/65 Purchase - Papers, Trustee actions, Budget, etc, 1965 -1969 (Box 30)
- 370 Planning (Box 30)
  - Site, 1973-1974
  - Trustees (2 folders), 1973
  - Financial/Dean's Council Packet, 1974